<resources>
    <string name="RX_VR_PERMISSION_ACTION_MANAGE_WRITE_SETTINGS_DO_NOT_ASK">RX_VR_PERMISSION_ACTION_MANAGE_WRITE_SETTINGS_DO_NOT_ASK</string>


    <string name="PerformanceHacksDescription">PLEASE READ CAREFULLY BEFORE CHANGING VALUES !
    </string>

    <string name="VR_RENDERING_MODES_WARNING">
        PLEASE READ CAREFULLY BEFORE CHANGING VALUES
    </string>
    <string name="VR_RENDERING_MODES_SUMMARY">
        To reduce latency in VR mode you can select one of the rendering modes below.\n
        Disable60FPSLock: Trick the OS into rendering at >60fps without any screen tearing.\n
        This works on most pixel devices Running Android 9 and above. If you get >60fps with this mode enabled (for 60hz screens)\n
        This mode works and I recommend using it. Else, use a different one.\n
    </string>

    <string name="Disable60FPSLock_Summary">
        Trick the OS into rendering at >60fps without any screen tearing.
        This works on most Pixel devices running Android 9 and above. If you get >60fps with this mode enabled (for 60hz screens)
        it works and I recommend using it. Else, use a different one.\n
    </string>

    <string name="DisbaleLowPersistenceModeDescription">Low persistence mode slightly decreases your perceived display response time
        (and therefore latency) but makes your screen flickery. Disable it here if you dont like it. Only has an effect when SuperSync is enabled.
    </string>

    <string name="SuperSyncDescription">Advanced VR rendering technique, modified for FPV-VR. Lowest input lag possible (8.3ms), without any visual imperfections
        like tearing. Has high performance and hardware requirements, that are only fulfilled on high-end phones. I recommend a Daydream-ready device.
        If you enable this technique on non-daydream ready phones, you might see stuttering and/or tearing.
    </string>
    <string name="DisableVSYNCDescription">
        Disables VSYNC (Vertical Sync). Reduces input lag to ~16.6ms@120fps or less, depending on your hardware (higher fps->less latency).
        WARNING: Has the negative side effect of Tearing (Visual imperfections) and wasted frames  It is up to you if you can live with tearing for a lower
        latency, but I definitely recommend enabling this option if available.
    </string>
    <string name="Disable60FPSLockDescription">
        VSYNC on (no tearing), but >60 OpenGL fps (lower latency). Input lag is at ~33.2ms@120fps.
        WARNING: when your phone has trouble rendering at >60fps, enabling this option can increase latency. Also, disabling VSYNC gives much lower latency.
    </string>
    <string name="MSAADescription">
        MSAA increases quality with very little performance loss.
        Which MSAA level to choose depends on your GPU power, screen resolution and magnification of your VR headset.
        Most modern tile-based GPUs can handle up to 4xMSAA with only 10-20perc. performance loss, while increasing quality significantly.
    </string>

</resources>
